motracmotorcycles.com 2018-12-20

# Privacy Statement | Motrac Motorcycles

We can only obtain personal information from you via the MOTRAC Motorcycles website if you choose to supply it to us by entering your information in the appropriate locations of this website. Your name, phone number and e-mail address are the personal information that we may collect from you. If you do not provide this information to us we will not be able to provide the additional information that you have requested. We may use your personal information to send news, information about our activities and general promotional material, which we believe, may be useful to you; monitor who is accessing the MOTRAC Motorcycles website or using services offered on the MOTRAC Motorcycles website; and profile the type of people accessing the MOTRAC Motorcycles website.

We utilize cookies, which enable us to monitor traffic patterns and to serve you more efficiently if you revisit this website. A cookie does not identify you personally but it does identify your computer. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie and this will provide you with an opportunity to either accept or reject it in any instance.

Your personal information may be shared with our related partners. We may engage third party contractors to perform services for us, which involve the contractor handling personal information we hold. Where we engage third party contractors to perform services for us, we prohibit the third party contractor from using personal information about you except for the specific purpose for which we supply it.

From time to time we may form partnerships with other organizations to bring you special offers, competitions, surveys and subscriptions and we may use other service providers in conducting our business. It may be necessary to disclose your personal information to these organizations and service providers.

We will not sell, rent or trade your personal information to a third party.

Other than as set out above, we will not disclose your personal information unless the disclosure is required by law; you have consented to our disclosure of the information; or we believe that the use or disclosure is reasonably necessary to assist a law enforcement agency or an agency responsible for government or public security in the performance of their functions.

We may transfer your personal information to foreign countries when we share your information with our related bodies corporate or service providers.

If you wish to comment on or query this privacy statement, or if you wish to make an inquiry regarding any personal information relating to you, which may be in our possession, do not hesitate to contact us.

**Security of Information**

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed as totally secure. Whilst we strive to protect such information, we do not warrant and cannot ensure the security of any information that you transmit to us. Accordingly, any information that you transmit to us is transmitted at your own risk.

Nevertheless, once we receive your transmission, we will take reasonable steps to preserve the security of such information. Commercial Electronic Messages By accepting these Terms of Use, you consent to us sending you commercial electronic messages where you provide us with your e-mail address over the MOTRAC Motorcycles website.

**Termination of Access**

We may terminate access to the MOTRAC Motorcycles website at any time without notice. Our disclaimer will nevertheless survive any such termination.

**Governing Law**

The laws in force in United States of America, State of Florida, govern these terms and conditions and any disputes will be decided only by the USA, FLORIDA courts.
